Now that we've dealt with the layout of an object's attributes, we can switch
既然我们已经处理了对象属性的布局，我们可以切换
gears and talk about how we layout its methods and how we implement dynamic dispatch.
并讨论我们如何布局它的方法，以及我们如何实现动态调度。
So, let's consider a dispatch called e.g where e here, let's say, is a class
那么，让我们考虑一个名为，例如，这里的e是一个类的调度
b. Okay? So what do we wanted to have happen? Well, we want to invoke the g
B，好吗？那么我们希望发生什么呢？好的，我们想调用g
method here in class b, okay? So that seems pretty straight forward. So now let's
方法，好吗？所以这看起来相当直截了当。所以现在让我们
consider a slightly more complicated example. What if we are invoking e.f of if
考虑一个稍微复杂一点的例子。如果我们调用的是IF的E.F.
we're calling the f method? Well, if we have a b object. Then we are going to want
我们要调用f方法？如果我们有一个b物体。那么我们就会想要
to evoke this method, this f method, okay, which is the f method to find in b. But if
为了调用这个方法，这个f方法，好的，这是在b中找到的f方法，但是如果
we have an a object, we want to be sure that we invoke this method, okay, this version
我们有一个a对象，我们想确保我们调用了这个方法，好的，这个版本
of f. Alright, and so, this f down here is said to be overridden. Okay. So, we
好的，那么这里的这个f被认为是被覆盖的。好吧。所以，我们
have redefined. Method f in class b and this definition replaces the method definition
重新定义了。类b中的方法f，并且此定义替换了方法定义
that b would otherwise have inherited from a so in particular in class
如果不是这样，b就会继承a so，特别是在班级中。
c, class c also have an f method okay and if we invoke the f method, if it turns out
类c也有一个f方法，如果我们调用f方法，如果结果是
that e here is a type c then which method should get involved? Well it would be this
这里的e是类型c，那么应该使用哪种方法呢？嗯，应该是这样的。
one. It would be the one defining class a so all three of these classes has an f method.
一。它将定义类a，因此所有这三个类都有一个f方法。
If the, if we do a dynamic dispatch on either a c or a object or execute
如果我们对c或对象执行动态分派或执行
the one defining class a. If we do the dispatch on the b object, we will execute
定义类a的那个。如果我们对b对象执行分派，我们将执行
the method defined in class b. Now every class has a fixed set of methods including
类b中定义的方法。现在每个类都有一组固定的方法，包括
the inherited methods. So if you, if you look, if I tell you the name of
继承的方法。所以如果你，如果你看，如果我告诉你
a class, then you know exactly which methods it has. Those methods never change
类，那么您就确切地知道它有哪些方法。这些方法永远不会改变
at runtime. Okay? So don't be confused here because overriding is something that's
在运行时。好吧?所以不要在这里感到困惑，因为凌驾于一切之上的东西
done at compile time is basically a static property. South compiler can figure
在编译时完成基本上是一个静电属性。南方编译器可以计算出
out even though you can redefine methods in subclasses the compiler can figure out
即使您可以在子类中重新定义方法，编译器也可以找出
a compile time all the methods of a particular class. Methods never change while
A编译时特定类的所有方法。方法在执行以下操作时从不更改
the prog ram is executing. Alright So, a dispatch tape of there's a table of
程序内存正在执行。好的，那么，一盘调度录像带上有一张桌子
some sort is used to index these methods and this is just in the ray of method entry
使用某种排序来索引这些方法，这只是在方法条目的射线中
point. So, essentially for every method of the class there's an entry in the
重点。因此，基本上对于类的每个方法，在
ray for that method. And just like with attributes, the method f is going to
雷用那个方法。就像属性一样，方法f将
live at the fixed offset. In the dispatch table for a class and all of its subclasses
生活在固定的偏移量上。在类及其所有子类的调度表中
so once we determine the position that a method lives in. It lives
所以一旦我们确定了方法所处的位置。它活着
in the dispatch table; it will stay there for any subclasses of that class. So let's
在调度表中；它将为该类的任何子类留在那里。所以让我们
take a look at our example again and just a reminder the structure of the example we
再看一下我们的示例，只是提醒一下我们的示例的结构
have class a and now we only really care about the method so class a define an f method
有a类，现在我们真正关心的是方法，所以a类定义了一个f方法
and then we have class b which inherits from a. And that define the g method.
然后我们有类b，它继承自a，它定义了g方法。
And then there was the class which also inherits from a which defines an h method.
然后还有一个类，它也是从定义h方法的a继承而来的。
Alright so those three classes and these methods, Okay? And so the dispatch table
好的，这三个类和这些方法，好吗？因此调度表
for class a only has one method in it so it's also at zero. We store a pointer
因为类a中只有一个方法，所以它也是零。我们存储一个指针
to the code for the f method define an a, okay? So this is actually literally
f方法的代码定义a，好吗？所以这实际上是字面意思
just a pointer to the first instruction of the code that will run method
只是指向将运行方法的代码的第一条指令的指针
a. So this is a pointer to the caller side or the calling sequence or the
a.所以这是指向调用方的指针，或者是指向调用序列的指针，或者是指向
label labeled instruction as the entry point for the method. Now, what about let's
将标记为Instruction的标签标记为该方法的入口点。现在，让我们
take a look next actually at class c. Okay? So class inherits from a. So what's
接下来我们来看看c班，好吗？所以类继承自。那么
going to happen with all the methods of a and they're going to be at the
所有的方法都会发生，他们会在
same off sets. So in particular, the f method will appear at offset zero in class
同样的抵销。因此，特别要注意的是，f方法将出现在类中的偏移量为零的位置
and this points to the same method as the one in a And so this inherits that method
中的方法指向相同的方法，因此它继承了该方法
from a and then class c defines its own method h and so in the next position of the
，然后类c定义了它自己的方法h，因此在
table goes the pointer to the code for h. And, you know, there have been more methods
表将指针指向h的代码。
defined in this classes than they would have appeared you know, laid out in
在这个类中定义的，而不是它们本来会出现的，您知道的，在
textual order just like for the attributes. So, if there have been, say, two
文本顺序与属性的顺序相同。所以，如果有，比方说，有两个
methods defined in a, then there will be two entries here fo r the first method
中定义的方法，则第一个方法在此处将有两个条目
and the second method define an a and then c define a three method then there will be
第二个方法定义a，然后c定义三个方法，那么将有
three more entries in the table and so on. Okay. Now the interesting case is what happens
表中还有三个条目，依此类推。好吧。现在有趣的情况是发生了什么
in class b. So in class b the f method is redefined and I forgot to indicate
在类b中。所以在类b中重新定义了f方法，但是我忘了指出
that so let me just indicate that up here so the f method, we have a new definition
那么让我来说明一下，在这里，f方法，我们有了一个新的定义
of the f method in class b. Okay so the important thing to see here is
类b中的f方法。好的，这里要看到的重要一点是
that the pointer to the code for the f method lives in the same position. It's still
f方法的代码指针位于同一位置。它现在还在
the first entry in the table, okay so the position of the f method in the dispatch
表中的第一个条目，好的，那么f方法在分派中的位置
table for class b is exactly the same that never changes. What's difference
类b的表是完全相同的，永远不会改变。有什么不同
is just the contents of that location. The first entry in the table here points to a
就是那个地方的东西。该表中的第一个条目指向一个
different function. It points to the method that was defined in b instead of the
功能不同。它指向在b中定义的方法，而不是
one that was defined in a. And then since b defines some additional methods or
在a中定义的方法。然后由于b定义了一些附加的方法或
one additional method that gets laid out after the methods for a. You may recall a
的方法之后布局的另一个方法。您可能还记得
while ago that we talked about the object header and we mentioned this thing called
而在前面，我们讨论了对象头，并且我们提到了名为
the dispatch pointer so this would remind ourselves what goes in the object header.
调度指针，所以这会提醒我们对象头中有什么。
There is the tag and then there is the size and then there was a dispatch pointer
先是标签，然后是大小，然后是分派指针
so And then following dispatch pointer where all the, all the attributes of the class
因此，然后跟随调度指针，其中类的所有、所有属性
And now this dispatch pointer is just a pointer to the table of methods for
现在这个分派指针只是一个指向的方法表的指针
that class, okay? So this would be a pointer to the table. That contains all the
那节课，好吗？所以这将是指向该表的指针。它包含所有
entries for the methods, all the entry points of the methods for that class. And
方法的条目，即该类的方法的所有入口点。和
the reason for using this level of in direction and so, why do we have this pointer
使用这一级别的In Direction的原因，那么，为什么我们有这个指针
to a separate table and so, why are the methods laid out like that when all
添加到一个单独的表中，那么，为什么所有的方法都是这样排列的呢？
the attributes are just embedded directly in the class And we could, if we
属性只是直接嵌入到类中，如果我们
wanted to just embed all the functions directly inside the object and, ad, you know,
我只想把所有的函数直接嵌入到对象中，而且，你知道，
out this whole table inside t object and, and not have this extra pointer that
在t对象和内部取出整个表，并且没有这个额外的指针
we have to, we have to maintain and follow And in the reason for this is th at the attributes
我们必须，我们必须保持和遵循，原因在于这些属性
are, can be updated. Okay, So, the attributes for a and object can be unique
都是，可以更新的。好的，因此，AND对象的属性可以是唯一的
object. Every object and have its own set of attributes so alright But the functions,
对象。每个对象都有自己的一组属性，所以好吧，但是函数，
the methods for an object never change. And so the same object table can be
对象的方法永远不会更改。因此，相同的对象表可以
shared Between all the objects of a given class. So if I have 100 a objects well
在给定类的所有对象之间共享。所以如果我有100a的物体
then I might have 100 different version of the attributes and so each a objects
那么我可能有100个不同版本的属性，所以每个都是对象
has its own copy of the attributes. But all those 100 a objects will
有自己的属性副本。但所有这100个a对象都会
have the same methods and I can save a lot of space by having them share a common
具有相同的方法，并且我可以通过让它们共享一个公共空间来节省大量空间
table of the methods And again every method of the class or every class is
表，同样，类的每个方法或每个类都
a sign and offset and we'll call that Os of f. In the dispatch table compiled times.
符号和偏移量，我们将在分派表编译时间中调用f的O。
So the job of the compiler to figure out all the methods of the class and
因此编译器的工作是找出类的所有方法和
then assign each of those methods, a fixed position, a fixed offset in that dispatch
然后在派单中为这些方法中的每一个分配一个固定位置、固定偏移量
table, So to wrap up, how do we implement dynamic dispatch? So let's say we
表，那么总而言之，我们如何实现动态调度呢？所以我们可以说我们
have a dispatch to an expression e and we're calling the f method. So, here's the,
对表达式e进行分派，我们将调用f方法。所以，这就是，
a slightly simplified version of the sequence of steps. So first, we evaluate the
步骤序列的略微简化的版本。因此，首先，我们评估
expression e and that's going to give us back an object x. Okay, and then we are
表达式e，它会给我们返回一个对象x。好的，然后我们
going to get the dispatch table for x, where that does come from. Well, it's in the
去拿x的调度表，它确实是从哪里来的。嗯，它在
header of x so we can just take the object x itself and we know that in every
头，所以我们可以只取对象x本身，我们知道在每个
object at the, in the third word there is a dispatch pointer for the, that's appropriate
对象，在第三个单词中，有一个用于的调度指针，这是合适的
to the class of x. So, we take that table and then we look up the entry point
到x的类。所以，我们取那张表，然后我们查找入口点
of f at the offset For f in that dispatch table And then we'll jump to that
的偏移量，然后我们跳到那个调度表中
to that address, okay? That's the entry point of the function and, and when we do
去那个地址，好吗？这是函数和的入口点，当我们这样做时
that, we're buying self to x. So the, the self parameter inside of the f method will
这就是说，我们把self买给x，所以f方法中的self参数将
be the x object.
成为x对象。